The hunter becomes the hunted.
Switchback is a thriller, mystery film directed by Jeb Stuart.
After FBI agent Frank Lacrosse believes his son was kidnapped by a notorious serial killer,
he travels to Amarillo, Texas, where he believes the murderer is in hiding.
Although officially taken off the case because of its personal significance to him, Frank
continues to pursue the killer, causing concern for local sheriff Buck Olmstead.
When another victim pops up at a nearby car garage, Frank knows that he is as
close as he'll ever be to tracking down the elusive killer.
FBI Special Agent Frank LaCrosse, played by Dennis Quaid.
Bob Goodall, played by Danny Glover.
Sheriff Buck Olmstead, played by R. Lee Ermey.
Lane Dixon, played by Jared Leto.
Deputy Nate Booker, played by Ted Levine.
Chief Jack McGinnis, played by William Fichtner.
Switchback is a 1997 American crime thriller film written and
directed by Jeb Stuart in his directorial debut.
It stars Dennis Quaid, Danny Glover, Jared Leto,
Ted Levine, William Fichtner and R.
An FBI agent tracks his son's kidnapper to Amarillo, Texas, where two
lawmen are seeking to use the case in their election bid.
The film explores themes of sheriff, texas, colorado, murder, young boy.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.